Bridge Line Historical Society; Collection mss129
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Maps, Blueprints, and Drawings, 1870-2004; 2; 613 items
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Susquehanna Division; Elevations through East Binghamton Yard in Conklin, NY (Reproduction of 1982 Map), Undated (Map-tube 461)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000483
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Track Schematic Binghamton-Scranton (Reproduction of 1980), Undated (Map-tube 362)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001085
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Track Schematic of Binghamton-Scranton (Reproduction of 1980 Map), Undated (Map-tube 264)
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Track Schematic of South End (Reproduction of 1975 Map), Undated (Map-tube 253)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000903
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Track Schematic of South End (Reproduction of 1982 Map), Undated (Map-tube 283)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001029
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Tracks Throughout Corporate History from April 23, 1823 to April 17, 1959, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000906
  - Delaware and Hudson Railway Corporation: Selected Northeast Rail Lines and Mileages (Reproduction of 1981 Map), Undated (Map-tube 369)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000979
  - Delaware and Hudson: Standard Grass Line (Reproduction of 1922 Map), Map Number 479, Undated (Flat-file 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000316
  - Depiction of a Train Car, No. 350, Undated (Map-tube 224)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001302
  - Diagram of Typical Method of Stacking Track Shims, Undated (Map-tube 379)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001104
  - Elimination of Grade Crossings in the City and Vicinity of Saratoga Springs, 1944 (Map-tube 33)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000064; Other Identification Number: J-38099
  - Erie Railroad Co., Jefferson Division: Cross-sections of Track and "A" Line in Connection with Proposed Reconstruction of Bridge No. 15.97, Thompson, PA, 1934 (Map-tube 94)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000096; Other Identification Number: E-36-2
  - Erie Railroad, Jefferson Division: H-1943 (9 sheets): 1- Location Plan; 2- Marking Diagram Railing; 3- Approach "E"; 4- Center Span; 5- Approach "F"; 6- Bent "B"; 7- Bent "A"; 8- List of Field Rivets and Bolts; 9- Bill of Floor Material, 1910 (Map-tube 11)
  - Existing Roundhouse: East Binghamton Yard, Conklin, N.Y., 1981 (Map-tube 134)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001233
  - Extension, R&S RR, Schenectady, Undated (Map-tube 39)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000026; Other Identification Number: 708-1502
  - First Map for Locomotive L.R. 844 A-1, Side Elevation, Undated (Map-tube 462)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000858
  - Floor Plan of Roundhouse in Binghamton, NY, 1954 (Map-tube 356)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000995; Other Identification Number: 39-858
  - Fort Worth and Denver City Railroad Company Water Gauge Blueprint, Number 103, Undated (Map-tube 201)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000512
  - Fort Worth and Denver City Railroad Company Water Gauge Blueprint, Number 115, Undated (Map-tube 203)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000511
  - Freight Traffic Density Diagram for Railroads in the New England District of Official Classification Territory (Part of L.F. Loree's Great Eastern Railway System), Undated (Map-tube 125)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000007
  - Freight Traffic Density Diagraph: Railroads Included in the Proposed Five Groups in Official Classification Territory, Undated (Map-tube 122)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000008A-BLA000008B
  - Full-Size Outline and Print Versions of "The D&H", Undated (Map-tube 49)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000054; Other Identification Number: 164-3371
  - G.T. Track[?], Rouses Point and Canada, Undated (Map-tube 119)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000101; Other Identification Number: 12-181
  - General Arrangement of Cupola "A" End (Reproduction of 1970 Map), Undated (Map-tube 460)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000852
  - General Plan of Public Service Commission Case #14882: Delaware & Hudson RR Corp., Champlain Division, Val section 14A: Map of South Quay and North Quay Street Crossings at Port Kent, NY, 1950 (Map-tube 107)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000100; Other Identification Number: 618-36877
  - Granville Coal Trestle, Undated (Map-tube 190)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001240; Other Identification Number: 34-2967
  - Graph Paper: G.I. Branch Masonry Canal Bridge (Working Sketch), Undated (Map-tube 110)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000097; Other Identification Number: 709-2213
  - Green Island Masonry Under Crossing, Undated (Map-tube 63)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000015; Other Identification Number: 705-2214
  - Green Island to Waterford Junction, 1922 (Map-tube 36)
  - Green Island to Waterford Junction: Office of the General Superintendent, Equipment and Way, Undated (Map-tube 37)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000010; Other Identification Number: 12-167
  - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railroad: Yard Map of Greenwich, NY (Reproduction of 1930 Map), Undated (Map-tube 421)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001370
  - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway Company: Johnsonville to Schuylerville, Proposed Bituminous Macadam Crossing on New Tomson-Clark's Mills Highway at Thomson, N.Y. (Reproduction of 1940 Map), Undated (Map-tube 208)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000553
  - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway Company: Main Track and Spurs at Big Falls, N.Y. (Ondawa) (Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 202)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000552A
  - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway Company: Main Track and Spurs at Big Falls, N.Y. (Ondawa) (Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 209)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000552
  - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway: Masonry Plan for 100ft. Turntable in Greenwich, NY (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 247)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001321
  - Hand-drawn Schematic of Binghamton Yard, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Hudson Co., Montreal Office, Window Advertisement Lettering (Montreal, P.Q.) (Reproduction of 1915 Drawing), Undated (Map-tube 19)
  - Hudson River [Area] NY: Albany and Vicinity, Showing Flooded Areas, 1913 (Map-tube 93)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000092; Other Identification Number: 79-24255
  - Hudson River Estates, Inc. Industrial and Real Estate Department: Map Showing Land Near Albany, 1945 (Map-tube 51)
    Other Identification Number: 5-A 5279
  - Hudson River Telephone Company, Proposed Plan of Crossing Green Island Bridge with Iron Pipe Conduit (Four Drawings), Undated (Map-tube 111)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000107; Other Identification Number: 12-2717
  - Hudson Valley Railway, Immediate Vicinity of Fort Miller; Shows Parts of Town of Northumberland; Includes Document Detailing Lands of A. L. Finne and Mary B. Finne, Undated (Map-tube 3)
    Other Identification Number: 709-3035
  - Incomplete Yard Map, Schenectady, NY, 1908-1909 (Glenville to Near Gas Company) (Map-tube 10)
  - Jour[?] Systems Map: Negarious [?] and Extra Print for Use in Map (Part of L.F. Loree's Great Eastern Railway System), Undated (Map-tube 126)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000018; Other Identification Number: P-V-53165
  - Land Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Saratoga Division Ballston Branch; Schenectady to Ballston Spa, Station 100+00 to Station 160+66.5 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 176)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001254
  - Location of Automatic Switch Heaters To Be Installed at "CB" Cabin Central Bridge, NY, 1955 (Map-tube 315)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001126
  - Location of Automatic Switch Heaters To Be Installed at "WN" Cabin South of Schenevus, NY, 1955 (Map-tube 349)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001131
  - Location of Switch Heaters "CB" Cabin in Central Bridge, BY, 1957 (Map-tube 325)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001114
  - Location of Switch Heaters "DJ" Cabin in Delanson, NY, 1957 (Map-tube 288)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001116
  - Location of Switch Heaters "WN" Cabin in Schenevus, NY, 1957 (Map-tube 327)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001115
  - Low Ceiling Installation A and B End, Undated (Map-tube 328)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Numbers: BLA000855
  - Machine Style "A" Crank Lead-out Schematic (Reproduction of 1951 Map), Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000882
  - Main Cab, Transverse Section, Undated (Map-tube 449)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000856
  - Main Line Track No. 3 To Be Removed Between "DE" and "WE" Cabins, 1955 (Map-tube 305)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001156
  - Manipulation Chart of Albany, NY to Watervliet Junction, NY, Undated (Map-tube 400)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000502
  - Map and Profile of the Troy Union Railroad Through City of Troy NY; Constructed 1853-54 (Reproduction of 1880s Map), Undated (Map-tube 6)
  - Map of Addison Junction, Undated (Map-tube 254)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000507
  - Map of Albany from Maiden Lane to North Ferry Street, Undated (Map-tube 586)
  - Map of Fort Edward Tracks, Undated (Map-tube 65)
    Other Identification Number: 708-1530
  - Map of Station Grounds at Peru, NY (Reproduction of 1904 Map), Undated (Map-tube 422)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001359
  - Map of Steamboat Lines, Albany Improvement (Reproduction of 1915 Map), Undated (Map-tube 56)
    Other Identification Number: 723-30941
  - Map of Steamboat Square, Undated (Map-tube 52)
    Other Identification Number: 2285-145
  - Map of the City of Carbondale, Lackawanna County, Pennsylvania, 1909 (Map-tube 35)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000013; Other Identification Number: 56-26
  - Map of the Route Adopted by the Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway Company from Greenwich, NY to Schuylerville, NY Signed by President and Chief Engineer of G&J, Undated (Map-tube 34)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000017; Other Identification Number: 532-23059
  - Map of the Village of Lake George in Warren County, 1910 (Map-tube 76)
    Other Identification Number: P-31-767
  - Map of Town of Cobleskill, Schoharie County, Undated (Map-tube 232)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000558-BLA000558A; Other Identification Number: 165-38825
  - Map of Uncultivated Woods, Map Number 486, Undated (Flat-file 2)
  - Map of United States Border with the Province of Quebec, Undated (Map-tube 279)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000506
  - Map Showing Movement of Manifest Train from Wilkes-Barre to a Point North of Hudson Interlocking Plant, Map Number 545, 1947 (Flat-file 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000900
  - Map Showing Railroad and Land of Hudson River Pulp & Paper Co., Palmer, NY (Corinth area) D&H Company; Sketch of Line on South Bank of Hudson River from Palmer Falls to So. Glens Falls (proposed line), 1904 (Map-tube 106)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000094; Other Identification Number: 12-2489
  - Map Showing the Connections of Utica[?], Undated (Map-tube 115)
  - Map Showing Tracks and Lands of the Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway Company at Thomson, Town of Greenwich, Washington County, NY, Undated (Map-tube 236)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000554A
  - Mass Diagram, Thurman to Warrensburg (Geological Profile), Undated (Map-tube 64)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000024; Other Identification Number: 709-3015
  - Miscellaneous Painting Diagram for Road Number 4101-4102, Alco Productions, Inc., 1958 (Map-tube 251)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000500
  - Miscellaneous Painting Diagram for Road Number 900-909, Alco Productions, Inc., 1958 (Map-tube 273)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000499
  - Miscellaneous Painting Diagram, Interstate RR RS3s Nos. 30-36, 38-39 (Reproduction of 1953 Diagram), Undated (Map-tube 13)
  - N.Y.G. & H.H.R.: Middle Division Troy Union Railroad Plan of Track Layout, Troy Station, 1904 (Map-tube 223)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA0001284; Other Identification Number: 36-913
  - New York Central Rail Road General Plan: Cantilever Signal Bridge for Two Tracks (Reproduction of 1915 Map), Undated (Map-tube 587)
  - New York Central System Application of Four Wheel Truck, Electric Locomotive Class S-2, Undated (Map-tube 457)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000859
  - Oneonta Hump Yard: Proposed Change of Grade, 1902 (Map-tube 98)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000081; Other Identification Number: 12-3427
  - Original Blueprint of Franklin Boilers No. 38, 39 and 40, 1946 (Map-tube 214)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000467
  - Part of the City of Albany Between Broadway and Church St. Showing the Original Division into Lots and Subdivisions (3 sheets), Undated (Map-tube 60)
    Other Identification Number: 3378-28
  - Pillsbury Company: Rouses Point Drawings (19 sheets), 1974 (Map-tube 167)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001251
  - Plan for Unidentified Train Station, Map Number 484, Undated (Flat-file 2)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001277
  - Plan for Unidentified Train Station in Albany, NY, Undated (Map-tube 147)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001413
  - Plan No. 15: Detail of Castings for East and West Viaducts, Undated (Map-tube 75)
    Other Identification Number: 66-27-229
  - Plan No. A: Proposed Track Arrangement, New River Line, Watervliet and Green Island, 1921 (Map-tube 123)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000012
  - Plan No. R38 (formerly 607): One Span Half Through Plate Girder Bridge, 32 Feet 10 Inch Extreme Length, Bridge No. 45, Penna. Div., of D&H C. Company at East Windsor, NY, 1901 (Map-tube 100)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000108; Other Identification Number: 66-27250
  - Plan of Coal Trestle for Schenectady Gas Company on Hamilton Street, Schenectady NY, Undated (Map-tube 430)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001371
  - Plan of Ironwork Bridge: Bridge 79 / Marion Breaker, Undated (Map-tube 87)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000083; Other Identification Number: 56-27240
  - Plan of Masonry for Bridge #50 (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 355)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001020
  - Portion of Valuation Map: Near Roaring Brook, PA, 1939 (Map-tube 102)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000056; Other Identification Number: PSC #6627-7027; Erie J-38099
  - Profile of Watervliet Cross Sections (Probably Part of 1921 Proposed Relocation), Undated (Map-tube 74)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000089
  - Profile of Connection: Proposed Clifton Park - Round Lake Road Undercrossing; Covers MPs A29 to A22, Undated (Map-tube 82)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000041; Other Identification Number: 465-35129
  - Profile of Green Island and West Troy Railroad, Line E to Albany, Undated (Map-tube 15)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000034
  - Profile of High-Level Line: Scheme A, Undated (Map-tube 84)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000063
  - Profile of Low Level Line Grade Crossings, Bridges Nos. 7 to 11, Scheme D (Watervliet area), Undated (Map-tube 118)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000103
  - Profile of Low Level Line, 16-foot Clearances, Scheme C; Albany to Waterford Junction, Undated (Map-tube 117)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000105
  - Profile of Low Level Line, Scheme B (Albany to Waterford Junction), Undated (Map-tube 77)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000106
  - Profile of Low Level Line, Scheme B (Along Hudson River, Albany to Waterford, Undated (Map-tube 18)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000023
  - Profile of Low Level Line, Scheme B (Along Hudson River, Albany to Waterford Approx.), Undated (Map-tube 72)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000093
  - Profile of Route Adopted by Greenwich & Johnsonville Railway Co., From Greenwich NY to Schuylerville, NY, 1901 (Map-tube 88)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000085; Other Identification Number: 12-2505
  - Profile Siding, West Waterford, NY, Undated (Map-tube 114)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000099; Other Identification Number: 12-2504
  - Profile: Greenwich & Johnsonville Railway From Greenwich, NY to Johnsonville, NY, 1902 (Map-tube 90)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000087; Other Identification Number: 118-V53035
  - Profile: Lake Saint Catherine Line, Undated (Map-tube 97)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000090; Other Identification Number: 12-2506
  - Profile: Mile S29 to S4 (Jefferson Branch over Ararat Summit to Jefferson Junction, Undated (Map-tube 85)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000098
  - Profile: Susquehanna Division, Binghamton to Albany, Sheet #5 of 7. (Oneonta to Barnerville), 1917 (Map-tube 104)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000067; Other Identification Number: 512-30977
  - Property at Steamboat Landing Albany, NY, Undated (Map-tube 55)
    Other Identification Number: 2285 1-A
  - Property on Quay Street Albany, NY, Undated (Map-tube 53)
    Other Identification Number: 2285-145 1-A
  - Property on Quay Street Albany, NY, Undated (Map-tube 54)
    Other Identification Number: 2285-145 A-2
  - Proposed Change of Line, North Albany to Green Island; Saratoga Division; Valuation Section No. V8, 1922 (Map-tube 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000019
  - Proposed Changes of Line of Central Railroad of New Jersey; Baltimore Tunnel Colliery (2 sheets), Undated (Map-tube 78)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000077; Other Identification Number: 12-20775
  - Proposed Cribbing Vicinity of Richmondville Account Stone Ballasting, 1955 (Map-tube 345)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000989
  - Proposed Glenville Yard, Scheme A; Val Sec 7B 7C, 1921 (Map-tube 129)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000002; Other Identification Number: P-31000
  - Proposed Glenville Yard, Scheme B; Val Sec 7B 7C, 1921 (Map-tube 127)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000005; Other Identification Number: P-31001
  - Proposed Glenville Yard, Scheme C; Val Sec 7B 7C: Susquehanna Division: Topography of Glenville [NY] and Vicinity, 1921 (Map-tube 120)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000003; Other Identification Number: P-31002
  - Proposed Glenville Yard, Scheme D; Val Sec 7B 7C, 1921 (Map-tube 128)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000001; Other Identification Number: P-31003
  - Proposed Glenville Yard, Scheme E; Val Sec 7B 7C: Susquehanna Division: Topography of Glenville [NY] and Vicinity, 1921 (Map-tube 121)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000004; Other Identification Number: P-31004
  - Proposed Grade Reductions; Profile: Final Projected Location, Richmondville Summit to Delanson Summit (Contains Extensive Notes on Back), 1917 (Map-tube 62)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000109; Other Identification Number: 549-28098
  - Proposed Line from Moreau Crossing to South Glens Falls (Map of Furnished R. R. Coms. Of South Glens Falls Branch), Undated (Map-tube 66)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000066; Other Identification: 12-2494
  - Proposed Operating Circuits for the Otsego Iron and Metal Corporation, Undated (Map-tube 431)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000474
  - Proposed Track Arrangement and Proposed Combined Troy - Watervliet Passenger Station at Congress Street Bridge (Part of Proposal to Move Rensselaer & Saratoga Main Line to Edge of Hudson River) (Reproduction of 1922 Map), Undated (Map-tube 124)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000016; Other Identification Number: 12-164
  - Proposed Track at Fonda, Nott Street (intersection) (Schenectady), Undated (Map-tube 67)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000021; Other Identification Number: 708-1494
  - Proposed Trestle for Glens Falls Portland Cement Company, Fifth Scheme (Three Sheets) (Reproduction of 1903 Map), Undated (Map-tube 394)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001395
  - Proposed Viaduct Over Boreas River, Undated (Map-tube 81)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000091; Other Identification Number: 12-2712
  - Public Service Case #4878: Grade Crossing Elimination of the Railroad Operated by the Delaware & Hudson Co. with the Highway Known as Jacob's Crossing, Town of Willsboro, Essex County. Jerry Hathaway (reputed owner). Multiple Sheets, 1928 (Map-tube 92)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000086; Other Identification Number: 182-32728
  - Railroads of the Capital District (Reproduction of 1931 Map), Undated (Map-tube 582)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000861
  - Ramapo Ajax Corporation: No. 31 Switch Stand, Map Number 542, Undated (Flat-file 3)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000272
  - Ramapo Iron Works / Pennsylvania Steel Co; Frogs and Toads: One Sheet Shows Intersection of Rutland Street Railway Co. with D&H RR; Six Sheets in Set; Collection of Drawings Showing Product Line, 1885; Undated (Map-tube 70)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000082; Other Identification Number: 709-3380
  - Resistor Data and Train Control Schematics, Undated (Map-tube 234)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000498
  - Retirement of Tool House in Collier, NY, 1957 (Map-tube 342)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001118
  - Revised Map of the Rail Roads of New York State (Reproduction of 1874 Map), Undated (Map-tube 454)
  - Right of Way and Track Map: Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Wilkes-Barre to Green Ridge, Station 12+51.9 to Station 65+32 (4 Sheets) (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 401)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001388
  - Right of Way and Track Map: Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany; Station 1979+46.3 to Station 2029+15.7 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 145)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001179
  - Right of Way and Track Map: Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany; Station 6090+84 to Station 6143+63 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 403)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001391
  - Right of Way and Track Map: Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway Company: Johnsonville to Schuylerville, Station 1048+03 to Station 1100+40 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 494)